Now, that the model has been created,
创建好模型后
we'd like to test it to see how well it's doing.
下面测试模型 看看模型的表现如何
If we click on the high level notebook,
点击高阶 notebook
we can remind ourselves how we went about it there.
看看是如何测试模型的
First, we created a transformer object,
首先 我们创建了 transformer 对象
in which we described the number of
我们在其中描述了虚拟机的数量
virtual machines and the type of virtual machine we wanted to use,
以及虚拟机的类型
and then we call it the transform method,
然后调用 transform 方法
which created a batch transform job which was then executed by SageMaker,
该方法创建了一个批转换作业 然后被 SageMaker 执行
just like when we train the model we will construct
就像训练模型一样
our own batch transform job in a low-level notebook.
我们将在低阶 notebook 中自己构建批转换作业
Going back to the low-level notebook and scrolling down,
回到低阶 notebook 并向下滚动
the first thing to notice is that just like in the training and in
首先要注意的是 就像在训练和模型创建步骤中一样
the model creation steps we have to name our transformed job.
我们需要命名转换作业
Also like the model and training job cases,
并且和模型创建及训练作业步骤一样
we have to make sure that the name is unique.
必须确保名称是唯一的
So again, we make sure to append a timestamp on the end of the transform_jobs_name.
我们在 transform_job_name 后面附加一个时间戳
Next we, need to describe the transformation job in detail.
接着需要详细描述训练作业
We begin by setting a name,
首先设置名称
choosing the model which we wish to use for the transformation job,
选择转换作业要使用的模型
we describe how many simultaneous transformations will occur at any given time.
指定在任何给定时间同时有多少个转换在运行
For now, we'll just use one,
暂时先设为 1
but if we had a very large dataset,
但是如果有非常大的数据集
maybe we'd like more than one to run at the same time.
或许需要同时运行多个转换作业
Next, we describe the maximum amount of data that is sent to our model at any given time.
接着指定在任何给定时间发送的最大数据量
If you need to you can increase this,
你也可以增加这个值
but for now we will just leave it at six.
暂时先保留为 6
In this case, we're choosing multi-record,
这里设为 MultiRecord
which means we want to send multiple records in each chunk of data.
表示在每份数据中发送多条记录
Then, we describe where we would like
然后指定
SageMaker to save the results of our batch transformed job.
SageMaker 将批转换作业的结果保存到何处
Once we've described the output we should also make sure to describe the input.
描述了输出之后 还需要描述输入
Here we're telling SageMaker that we are sending it
我们告诉 SageMaker 我们将向其发送 CSV 数据
CSV data that we can break the data up line by line
如果数据太多 一次发送太大的话
in case the data is too large to send in a single chunk and where
我们可以按行拆分数据
the data is located in particular on S3 in this location.
然后指定数据所在的位置 即 S3 上的这个文件夹里
Lastly, we tell SageMaker what sort of machine to use when running the transform job.
最后 告诉 SageMaker 在什么样的虚拟机上运行转换作业
Now, that we have specified all of the parameters of our transformation job,
指定了转换作业的所有参数后
it's time to ask SageMaker to create the job.
下面要求 SageMaker 创建转换作业
Just like in the training case,
就像在训练步骤中一样
SageMaker is now working on creating and executing that transform job in the background.
SageMaker 现在正在后台创建和执行转换作业
So, in order to get some visual representation of what's going on,
为了直观地了解后台发生的情况
we need to call the weight for transform job method.
我们需要调用 wait_for_transform_job 方法
Now, we just need to wait for the transform job to complete.
现在等着转换作业运行完毕
Now, that the transform job is completed,
转换作业运行完毕后
we can take a look at the results.
我们来看看结果
First, we make sure to copy the output from
首先 需要将转换作业的输出
our transform job to the local notebook instance,
复制到本地 notebook 实例中
and then we create an edge graph to take a look to see how it's doing.
然后绘制图形 看看运行效果
It turns out not too bad.
结果并不糟糕